

GIULIO GOLA

iOS, Flutter & Full-stack
Web Developer
Data Scientist
Music Producer

About Me

Dynamic, agile and flexible mindset with a strong passion for coding, data and music. Proactive problem-solver: I find a way to make things work. Team-oriented, but also solo worker. Tennis fanatic. And I like to cook.

Contacts

• Via Calcari 59, 37023 Grezzana (VR), Italy

+39 327 5627274 / +49 152 08986316

ggola80@gmail.com

Expertise

iOS: Xcode, Swift 5, CoreML, CreateML, ARKit 1-2

Flutter: Android Studio, Dart 2

Web: Atom, HTML5, CSS3, JS ES6, jQuery, Bootstrap 4, Node / Express

Databases: MongoDB, Firebase, SqLite

UI/UX Design tool: Sketch, InVision

Data Science: Matlab, R, Neural Networks, Fuzzy Logic, Genetic

Algorithms

Education

iOS/ Flutter/ Web development courses (2018-2019) London App Brewery, UK

Music Production/Sound Engineer Diploma (2013-2014) dBs Music, Berlin, Germany

PhD - Risk Analysis (2006-2009)

Polytechnic of Milan, Italy/ Institute for Energy Technology, Norway

Bachelor and Master - Nuclear Engineering (1999-2005) Polytechnic of Milan, Italy

Experience

iOs/Flutter/Full-Stack Web Developer (2018-Present) Freelance (Verona, Italy/ Remote)

Some of my work is on my GitHub repo.

Co-Founder (2017-Present)

Tixeet /// Live Music Crowdfunded (Verona, Italy)

Mixing tech and music: co-founder, designer and developer at tixeet.com, the crowdfunding platform for live music events.

Consultant (2015)

Optimeering AS (Oslo, Norway)

Uncertainty models for inter/intra-day energy market bidding.

Founder/Music Producer/Sound Engineer (2013-2017) Legato Studio (Berlin, Germany)

When I decided to turn my passion for music into a job I opened a recording and mixing <u>studio</u>. Some of the production <u>here</u>.

Lead Engineer (2012-2013)

General Electric Oil & Gas (Firenze, Italy)

Remote Monitoring & Diagnostic group. Development of neural networks for gas turbine monitoring and maintenance optimisation.

Lead/Senior Researcher (2009-2012)

Institute for Energy Technology (Halden, Norway)

System Interface & Design group. Neural networks for nuclear signal monitoring and diagnostics. Functional and prognostic models for critical components. List of publications.

Researcher/Patent Co-Owner (2009-2011)

First Sensing AS (Oslo, Norway)

Neural networks-based technology for parameter virtual estimation applied to air and water quality monitoring.